A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, Rockefeller University Press, Journal of General Physiology, Editorial Correspondence, Series 2 FA925
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Editorial Correspondence, 2
  - GP #4287: Pinto and Ostroy (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - GP #4288: Rose, Nahrworld etc. (Box 52, Folder 29)
  - GP #4289: Lakshminarayanaiah (Box 52, Folder 30)
  - GP #4290: Rae and Eisenberg (Box 52, Folder 31)
  - GP #4291: LeBreton and Hoffmann (Box 52, Folder 32)
  - GP #4292: Brown (Box 52, Folder 33)
  - GP #4293: Vergara and Rapoport (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - GP #4294: Plishker and Gitelman (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - GP #4295: Haak, Keinhans etc. (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - GP #4296: Sigel, Crompton etc. (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - GP #4297: Moss and Halpern (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - GP #4298: Cahalan and Begenisich (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - GP #4299: Kirby and Enroth-Cugell (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - GP #4300: Uchikawa and Borle (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - GP #4301: Uchikawa and Borle (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - GP #4302: Kutyna and Bernard (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - GP #4303: Harosi (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - GP #4304: Brodie and Bownds (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - GP #4305: Dahl and Christof (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - GP #4306: Rothman and Strumwasser (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - GP #4307: Rothman and Strumwasser (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - GP #4308: Tayal (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - GP #4309: Benos, Simon, Mandel (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - GP #4310: Yamaguchi, Horiuchi (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - GP #4311: Lorkovic (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - GP #4312: Helman, Koeppen, etc. (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - GP #4313: Andersen, Finkelstein (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - GP #4314: Contreras (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - GP #4315: Arch, Earley and Smock (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - GP #4316: Shrager (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - GP #4317: Malan and Inesi (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - GP #4318: Peter M. Cala (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - GP #4319: Inoue, Pant, Gainer (Box 53, Folder 27)
  - GP #4320: Costanzo and Mozell (Box 53, Folder 28)
  - GP #4321: Mackie (Box 53, Folder 29)
  - GP #4322: Weiss, Goldman (Box 53, Folder 30)
  - GP #4323: Quist and Roufogalis (Box 53, Folder 31)
  - GP #4324: Imanish and Surawicz (Box 53, Folder 32)
  - GP #4325: Bernich and Rubenstein (Box 53, Folder 33)
  - GP #4326: Schein, Bennett etc. (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - GP #4327: Schein (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - GP #4328: Suarez-Kurtz et.al. (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - GP #4329: Suarez- Kurtz etc. (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - GP #4330: Stahl, Neuhoff etc. (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - GP #4331: Finkelstein (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - GP #4332: Finkelstein (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - GP #4333: Proverbio and Hoffman (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - GP #4334: Coplon, Steele etc. (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - GP #4335: Sabeth and Rahman (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - GP #4336: Ebert and Goldman (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - GP #4337: Castranova and Miles (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - GP #4338: Gola (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - GP #4339: Gola (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - GP #4340: Ueda, Kurihara etc. (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - GP #4341: Deitmer and Rathmayer (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - GP #4342: Mason (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - GP #4343: Brink and Barr (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - GP #4344: Weisblat, Byerly etc. (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - GP #4345: Yeh, Oxford etc. (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - GP #4346: Helman and Fisher (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - GP #4347: Koketsu and Kuba (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - GP #4348: Koketsu and Kuba (Box 54, Folder 23)
  - GP #4349: De Weer (Box 54, Folder 24)
  - GP #4350: David McCall (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - GP #4351: Barlow and Kaplan (Box 54, Folder 26)
  - GP #4352: Miura, Hoffman etc. (Box 54, Folder 27)
  - GP #4353: Hunter, Wong etc. (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - GP #4354: Brahm (Box 54, Folder 29)
  - GP #4355: DeClerck, Claes etc. (Box 54, Folder 30)
  - GP #4356: Schauf, Pencek etc. (Box 54, Folder 31)
  - GP #4357: Mulieri and Parsons (Box 54, Folder 32)
  - GP #4358: Kennedy and Deweer (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - GP #4359: Eldred, Hoffert etc. (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - GP #4360: Mattiazzi and Cingolani (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - GP #4361: Lewis (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - GP #4362: Johnson and Scarpa (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - GP #4363: Crooks and Cooke (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - GP #4364: Bozler (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - GP #4365: Bournaud, Mambrini (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - GP #4366: Fitts and Holloszy (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - GP #4367: Dunham (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - GP #4368: Fein and Sharlton (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - GP #4369: McAllister (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - GP #4370: Sanders (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - GP #4371: Wu and Wong (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - GP #4372: Binstock (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - GP #4373: Beauwens and Al-Awqati (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - GP #4374: Dowling and Ripps (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - GP #4375: Welling, Welling etc. (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - GP #4376: Blatt (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - GP #4377: Gordon and Ridgway (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - GP #4378: Parker, Castranova (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - GP #4379: Graham and Gordon (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - GP #4380: Zeidler and Kim (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - GP #4381: Clusin and Bennett (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - GP #4382: Clusin and Bennett (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - GP #4383: Harris and Stark (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - GP #4384: Robinson (Box 55, Folder 27)
  - GP #4385: Gilai and Kirsch (Box 55, Folder 28)
  - GP #4386: Mandel (Box 55, Folder 29)
  - GP #4387: Yeh and Narahashi (Box 55, Folder 30)
  - GP #4388: Weeden (Box 55, Folder 31)
  - GP #4389: Mahler and Rogel (Box 55, Folder 32)
  - GP #4390: Mahler and Rogel (Box 55, Folder 33)
  - GP #4391: Nuccitelli, Poo etc. (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - GP #4392: Melnick, Latorre etc. (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - GP #4393: Noble, Lacher etc. (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - GP #4394: Sheridan and Lester (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - GP #4395: Lester, Koblin etc. (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - GP #4396: Cabantchik etc. (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - GP #4397: Shapiro (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - GP #4398: Shapiro (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - GP #4399: Takeda (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - GP #4400: Brin and Ripps (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - GP #4401: Trowbridge (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - GP #4402: Al-Awqati et.al. (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - GP #4403: Bernstein (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - GP #4404: Schwartz and Kado (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - GP #4405: Stephenson and Podolsky (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - GP #4406: Stephenson and Podolsky (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - GP #4407: Fohlmeister et.al. (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - GP #4408: Fohlmeister (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - GP #4409: Fohlmeister et.al. (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - GP #4410: Daniel L. Alkon and Tadashi Akaike (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - GP #4411: Palade and Barchi (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - GP #4412: Feit and Bass (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - GP #4413: Zamir (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - GP #4414: Koch and Gilliband (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - GP #4415: O?Brien, Theodore etc. (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - GP #4416: Candia, Montoreano (Box 56, Folder 26)
  - GP #4417: Hornung and Mozell (Box 56, Folder 27)
  - GP #4418: Kim and Luthra (Box 56, Folder 28)
  - GP #4419: Knauf, Furhmann etc. (Box 56, Folder 29)
  - GP #4420: Shigeto, Vereecke (Box 56, Folder 30)
  - GP #4421: Murayama et.al. (Box 56, Folder 31)
  - GP #4422: Paulson, Hertz etc. (Box 56, Folder 32)
  - GP #4423: Mullins, Brinley etc. (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - GP #4424: Saunders and Brown (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - GP #4425: Brown and Saunders (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - GP #4426: Woodruff, Bownds etc. (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - GP #4427: James A. Schafer (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - GP #4428: Jacquez and Foster (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - GP #4429: Pollack (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - GP #4430: Hille (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - GP #4431: Hille (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - GP #4432: Kirchberger, Hechter (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - GP #4433: Garrick and Redwood (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - GP #4434: Valenzeno and Hoshiko (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - GP #4435: Alkon and Akaike (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - GP #4436: Schmidt and McManus (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - GP #4437: Schmidt and McManus (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - GP #4438: Schmidt and McManus (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - GP #4439: Miller and Steinberg (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - GP #4440: Wilson, Erecinska (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - GP #4441: Siep (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - GP #4442: Charlton and Bittner (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - GP #4443: Charlton and Bittner (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - GP #4444: Holz (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - GP #4445: Nagel, Helman, Fisher (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - GP #4446: de Villafranca (Box 57, Folder 24)
  - GP #4447: Goldsmith and Wehner (Box 57, Folder 25)
  - GP #4448: Deth and Casteels (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - GP #4449: Abercrombie and Sjodin (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - GP #4450: Baumgarten, Isenberg, etc. (Box 57, Folder 28)
  - GP #4451: Bolitho Donaldson (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - GP #4452: Warth and Desforges (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - GP #4453: Droogmans, Raeymaekers (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - GP #4454: Wiggins (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - GP #4455: Lodge (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - GP #4456: Ozeki and Osada (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - GP #4457: Krausz and Friesen (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - GP #4458: Rdel, Taylor etc. (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - GP #4459: Simon (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - GP #4460: Chan and Naka (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - GP #4461: Kinsey and Hightower (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - GP #4462: Fein and Charlton (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - GP #4463: Waloga and Pak (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - GP #4464: Ciani, Krasne, etc. (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - GP #4465: S.Hagiwara (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - GP #4466: Wong et.al. (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - GP #4467: Lodge and Daniel (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - GP #4468: Treistman and Schwartz (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - GP #4469: Kleinzeller and Dubyak (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - GP #4470: DiPolo (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - GP #4471: Palade and Barchi (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - GP #4472: Loh and Gainer (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - GP #4473: Gutknecht, Bisson (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - GP #4474: Cala, Cogswell etc. (Box 58, Folder 24)
  - GP #4475: Williams and Gale (Box 58, Folder 25)
  - GP #4476: Armstrong and Bezanilla (Box 58, Folder 26)
  - GP #4477: Armstrong and Bezanilla (Box 58, Folder 27)
  - GP #4478: Lewis, Eaton, Clausen (Box 58, Folder 28)
  - GP #4479: Yamaguchi and Twarog (Box 58, Folder 29)
  - GP #4480: Lisman and Bering (Box 58, Folder 30)
  - GP #4481: Kenyon and Gibbons (Box 58, Folder 31)
  - GP #4482: Kenyon and Gibbons (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - GP #4483: Sherman and Rossner (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - GP #4484: Fein and Charlton (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - GP #4485: Requena, Dipolo et.al. (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - GP #4486: Brinley, Tiffert etc. (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - GP #4487: Kirsch, Nichols, etc. (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - GP #4488: Moody (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - GP #4489: Putney and Parod (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - GP #4490: Oakley (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - GP #4491: Finkelstein (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - GP #4492: Brink and Dewey (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - GP #4493: Schumperli (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - GP #4494: Shimada (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - GP #4495: Meredith and Moulton (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - GP #4496: Vestergaard-Bogind etc. (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - GP #4497: Lantz, Wong and Mauro (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - GP #4498: Miller and Morchen (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - GP #4499: Cabantchik and Ginsburg (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - GP #4500: Lipton, Ostroy etc. (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - GP #4501: Lipton, Rasmussen (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - GP #4502: Stieve, Bruns, etc. (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - GP #4503: Kohlhardt, Mnich (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - GP #4504: Flood and Wilkens (Box 59, Folder 23)
  - GP #4505: Wise (Box 59, Folder 24)
  - GP #4506: Lassignal and Martin (Box 59, Folder 25)
  - GP #4507: Gilles-Baillien (Box 59, Folder 26)
  - GP #4508: Emil Bozler (Box 59, Folder 27)
  - GP #4509: Lauf, Stiehl and Joiner (Box 59, Folder 28)
  - GP #4510: Mullins (Box 59, Folder 29)
  - GP #4511: Roy and Okada (Box 59, Folder 30)
  - GP #4512: Wu and Pak (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - GP #4513: Alkon, Akaike etc. (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - GP #4514: Wolosin, Ginsburg, etc. (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - GP #4515: Callahan and Goldstein (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - GP #4516: French and Wells (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - GP #4517: Pennock and Goldman (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - GP #4518: Pepse and Lisman (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - GP #4519: Mandel (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - GP #4520: Schultz and Valentine (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - GP #4521: Gadsby and Cranefield (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - GP #4522: Minke and Kirschfeld (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - GP #4523: Ramon and Moore (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - GP #4524: Stefano, Catapane, etc. (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - GP #4525: Plishker and Gitelman (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - GP #4526: Klingman and Chappell (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - GP #4527: Frank Baylin (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - GP #4528: Baylin and Moulton (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - GP #4529: ter Keurs, etc. (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - GP #4530: Alkon, etc. (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - GP #4531: Kato et.al. (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - GP #4532: Ostroy (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - GP #4533: Reed (Box 60, Folder 22)
  - GP #4534: Minke and Kirschfeld (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - GP #4535: Maugan, Low, etc. (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - GP #4536: Pant, Yoshioka, etc. (Box 60, Folder 25)
  - GP #4537: Gordon, Shapley, etc. (Box 60, Folder 26)
  - GP #4538: Shapley and Gordon (Box 60, Folder 27)
  - GP #4539: Bayer and Barlow (Box 60, Folder 28)
  - GP #4540: Wormington and Cone (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - GP #4541: Gutknecht et.al. (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - GP #4542: Shukla and Agrawal (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - GP #4543: Parker (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - GP #4544: Revis (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - GP #4545: Gale and Williams (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - GP #4546: Easton and Swenberg (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - GP #4547: Ryan and Barr (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - GP #4548: Aizawa and Matsuoka (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - GP #4549: Muhl, Grim, etc. (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - GP #4560: Boupaep, Fischbarg (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - GP #4561: Ping-Lu Li, Wayne, etc. (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - GP #4562: Aswad, Dana W. (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - GP #4563: Safford, Bassingthwaighte and Bassingthwaighte (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - GP #4564: Fraioli and Barlow (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - GP #4565: Moore and Arispe (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - GP #4566: Li and De Sousa (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - GP #4567: Sevcik (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - GP #4568: Fletcher (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - GP #4569: Cohen and Murphy (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - GP #4570: Ruwart, Kaminski, etc. (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - GP #4571: Mahler (Box 61, Folder 22)
  - GP #4562: Mahler (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - GP #4563: Mahler (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - GP #4564: Dahl (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - GP #4565: Nathan and DeHaan (Box 61, Folder 26)
  - GP #4566: Stephenson (Box 61, Folder 27)
  - GP #4567: Nassar-Gentina etc. (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - GP #4568: Gesteland etc. (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - GP #4569: Scubon- Mulieri etc. (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - GP #4570: Furman and Barchi (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - GP #4571: Katz, Swanson and Reuben (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - GP #4572: Pepperberg et.al. (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - GP #4573: Lee and Akaike etc. (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - GP #4574: Akaike, Lee etc. (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - GP #4575: Kamm, Zatzman, Jones (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - GP #4576: Kamm, Zatzman, etc. (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - GP #4577: Oxford, Wu, Narahashi (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - GP #4578: Russell and Brodwich (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - GP #4579: Takenaka, Horie etc. (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - GP #4580: McLean and Sperelakis (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - GP #4581: Gerolf Gros, Harry S. Rollema, Wolgang Jelkmann, Hanne Gros, Christian Bauer and Waldemar Moll (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - GP #4582: Kenyon and Gibbons (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - GP #4583: Crone et.al. (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - GP #4584: Jones (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - GP #4585: Chen and Walser (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - GP #4586: Caputo and Dipolo (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - GP #4587: Brinley, Tiffert (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - GP #4588: Saida and Nonomura (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - GP #4589: Hellman, Nagel, etc. (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - GP #4590: Delamere and Paterson (Box 62, Folder 24)
  - GP #4591: Mrose and Ritchie (Box 62, Folder 25)
  - GP #4592: Gulati and Podolsky (Box 62, Folder 26)
  - GP #4593: Lantz and Mauro (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - GP #4594: Requena (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - GP #4595: Alkon, Grossman (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - GP #4596: Muramatsu, Kumamoto (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - GP #4597: Loo, McLarnon, etc. (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - GP #4598: Loo, McLarnon, Vaughan (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - GP #4599: Loo, McLarnon etc. (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - GP #4600: Loo, McLarnon (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - GP #4601: Pandey, Tosteson etc. (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - GP #4602: Sarkadi, Tosteson etc. (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - GP #4603: DeClerck, Claes, etc. (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - GP #4604: Lipton, Beswick etc. (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - GP #4605: Hahin and Goldman (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - GP #4606: Goldman and Hahin (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - GP #4607: Loiselle and Gibbs (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - GP #4608: Funder, Tosteson etc. (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - GP #4609: Sjodin and Abercrombie (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - GP #4610: McCann and Stibitz (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - GP #4611: Cohen, Hall and Ferrendelli (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - GP #4612: Huang, Catterall (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - GP #4613: Jackson, Williamson etc. (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - GP #4614: Kenyon and Gibbons (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - GP #4615: Masukawa and Albuquerque (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - GP #4616: Jay Z. Yeh (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - GP #4617: Barden et. al. (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - GP #4618: Lipetz (Box 63, Folder 26)
  - GP #4619: Blaustein et.al. (Box 63, Folder 27)
  - GP #4620: Blaustein et.al (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - GP #4621: West and Bernard (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - GP #4622: Brodie, Knight etc. (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - GP #4623: Brodie, Knight etc. (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - GP #4624: Hunt, Wilkinson etc. (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - GP #4625: Chapman and Johnson (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - GP #4626: Ramon and Moore (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - GP #4627: Oertel, Schein, etc. (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - GP #4628: Thompson and Dawson (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - GP #4629: Fabiato and Fabiato (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - GP #4630: Nordmann and Dyball (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - GP #4631: Knauf, Ship etc. (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - GP #4632: Knauf, Breuer, etc. (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - GP #4633: Grinstein, McCulloch (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - GP #4634: Hille and Schwarz (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - GP #4635: Rhoads and Epstein (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - GP #4636: Olson and Cazort (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - GP #4637: Holz (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - GP #4638: McClellan and Winegrad (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - GP #4639: Wu, Sides, Narahashi (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - GP #4640: Benison (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - GP #4641: Mullins (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - GP #4642: Torok, Vizi and Knoll (Box 64, Folder 23)
  - GP #4643: Marechal and Plaghki (Box 64, Folder 24)
  - GP #4644: Castranova and Hoffman (Box 64, Folder 25)
  - GP #4645: Clusin and Bennett (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - GP #4646: Clusin and Bennett (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - GP #4647: Swartz and Henn (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - GP #4648: Hobbs and Dunham (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - GP #4649: Benos and Tosteson (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - GP #4650: Bozler (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - GP #4651: Levin, Levin and Solomon (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - GP #4652: Hashimoto, Hauswirth (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - GP #4653: Hauswirth, et.al. (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - GP #4654: Lab (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - GP #4655: Lester (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - GP #4656: Spitzer and Hogan (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - GP #4657: Moore and Arispe (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - GP #4658: Weinstein and Stephenson (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - GP #4659: Vergara, Bezanilla etc. (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - GP #4660: Schoenberg and Wells (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - GP #4661: Rosenberg and Finkelstein (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - GP #4662: Rosenberg and Finkelstein (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - GP #4663: Maryanna P. Henkart and Phillip G. Nelson (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - GP #4664: Phillip G. Nelson and Maryanna P. Henkart (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - GP #4665: DiPolo (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - GP #4666: Engbretson et.al. (Box 65, Folder 22)
  - GP #4667: Witkovsky et.al. (Box 65, Folder 23)
  - GP #4668: George, Lathers and Teres (Box 65, Folder 24)
  - GP #4669: Wong, Knight and Dodge (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - GP #4670: Wong and Knight (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - GP #4671: Stein, Brammer etc. (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - GP #4672: E.W. Ballou (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - GP #4673: W.G.L. Kerrick, D.A. Malencik, P.E. Hoar, R.L. Coby, S. Pocinwong, and E.H. Fischer (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - GP #4674: Zamir (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - GP #4675: Farquarson (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - GP #4676: Benos, Mandel, etc. (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - GP #4677: Wunk and Werblin (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - GP #4678: Krasner (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - GP #4679: Faelli, Esposito, etc. (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - GP #4680: Nelson (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - GP #4681: Robert D. Prusch and Jo Ann Hannafin (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - GP #4682: Prusch (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - GP #4683: Lisman and Strong (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - GP #4684: Mounier and Vassort (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - GP #4685: Goria and Mauro (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - GP #4686: Victor and Shapley (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - GP #4687: Evans, Naylor and Quinton (Box 66, Folder 18)
  - GP #4688: Lau, Caswell and Garcia (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - GP #4689: Horackova and Vassort (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - GP #4690: Parisi et.al. (Box 66, Folder 21)
  - GP #4691: Contreras and Frank (Box 66, Folder 22)
  - GP #4692: Ken Vaca and Guillermo Pilar (Box 66, Folder 23)
  - GP #4693: Ismail- Feige, Bissel and Edelman (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - GP #4694: Krauss and Naka (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - GP #4695: Kirby (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - GP #4696: Spring and Hope (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - GP #4697: Saito, Kondo and Toyoda (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - GP #4698: Schiff and Overweg (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - GP #4699: Panet and Atlan (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - GP #4700 Minke and Kirschfield (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - GP #4701: Brinley, Mullins, etc. (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - GP #4702: Degnan and Zadunaisky (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - GP #4703: Miller et.al. (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - GP #4704: Miller et.al. (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - GP #4705: Miller et.al. (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - GP #4706: Miller et.al. (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - GP #4707: Cox and Alvarado (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - GP #4708: Kroeker (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - GP #4709: Zwas (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - GP #4710: Alpern and Zwas (Box 67, Folder 18)
  - GP #4711: Jaffe, Gould-Somero etc. (Box 67, Folder 19)
  - GP #4712: James Maylie (Box 67, Folder 20)
  - GP #4713: Donovan and LaTorre (Box 67, Folder 21)
  - GP #4714: Ono and Nakajima (Box 67, Folder 22)
  - GP #4715: Coleman and Coleman (Box 67, Folder 23)
  - GP #4716: Kniffki, Klaus-D. (Box 67, Folder 24)
  - GP #4717: Woodruff and Bownds (Box 67, Folder 25)
  - GP #4718: Curry (Box 67, Folder 26)
  - GP #4719: Koike and Nagata (Box 67, Folder 27)
  - GP #4720: Reuss, etc. (Box 67, Folder 28)
  - GP #4721: Wieth and Tosteson (Box 67, Folder 29)
  - GP #4722: Crescitelli (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - GP #4723: Kostyuk et.al. (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - GP #4724: Gunn and Frohlich (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - GP #4725: Tosteson and Wieth (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - GP #4726: Castranova, Weiss (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - GP #4727: Castranova, etc. (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - GP #4728: Ben-Sasson and Grover (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - GP #4729: Page and Surdyk-Droske (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - GP #4730: Benolken, Wheeler (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - GP #4731: Narvarte and Finn (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - GP #4732: Elmer T. Schmeisser and William W. Dawson (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - GP #4733: Weerasuriya, Rapoport and Taylor (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - GP #4734: Akaike and Alkon (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - GP #4735: Rae and Eisenberg (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - GP #4736: Pu and Dowling (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - GP #4737: Moss and Julian (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - GP #4738: Kawai, Abe, Mori etc. (Box 68, Folder 17)
  - GP #4739: Freedman and Hoffman (Box 68, Folder 18)
  - GP #4740: Freedman and Hoffman (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - GP #4741: Watanabe etc. (Box 68, Folder 20)
  - GP #4742: Lebaco and Homsher (Box 68, Folder 21)
  - GP #4743: Toribara (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - GP #4744: Lambert, Gladden, etc. (Box 68, Folder 23)
  - GP #4745: Bozler (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - GP #4746: Homsher et.al. (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - GP #4747: Brown, Lee et.al. (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - GP #4748: Catterall (Box 69, Folder 4)